const monthLengths = [
    {
        question: 'Styczeń',
        answers: ['31'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Luty',
        answers: ['28', '29'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Marzec',
        answers: ['31'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Kwiecień',
        answers: ['30'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Maj',
        answers: ['31'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Czerwiec',
        answers: ['30'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Lipiec',
        answers: ['31'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Sierpień',
        answers: ['31'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Wrzesień',
        answers: ['30'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Październik',
        answers: ['31'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Listopad',
        answers: ['30'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Grudzień',
        answers: ['31'],
    },
];

export default monthLengths;
